

CALVINCE AJWANG

ADMINISTRATOR/TECHNOLOGY ARCHITECT

OBJECTIVE

To seek relevant and challenging positions in an enabling corporate environment; where my current qualifications, abilities and experience would be an asset to the organization.

Working in a company will offer me an opportunity for personal growth, skills acquisition and job enrichment while being productive.

SKILLS/ABILITIES

- Cloud Computing Executive.
- Operating certain Equipment and Machinery
- Book Keeping and accounting Management
- Customer Service
- > Time Management
- Storage systems and management
- Adaptability
- Data Base Management

EDUCATION

INSTITUTE OF ADVANCE TECHNOLOGY (IAT) 8TH AUGUST 2020 TO PRESENT

<u>Diploma in Information Technology</u> <u>Areas of Study</u>

➤ Business Skills

EXPERIENCE

<u>CLEANING AND FUMIGATION SUPERVISOR • PMCS • 02/07/2014 – 04/12/2015</u>

- Establishment of cleaning standards and procedures for workers and ensure adherence to these standards and procedures
- > Coaching and developing employees/cleaners
- > Scheduling and assigning specific duties/roles to cleaners and also ensuring that they are carried out expertly
- Inspection of cleaning equipment on a regular basis so as to know when they are worn-out and also request for replacement
- > Controlling and monitoring the usage of cleaning materials so as to avoid or minimize waste and/or misuse
- > Providing necessary assistance to the colleagues and steward in general.
- > General store keeper and controller.

FRONT OFFICE MANAGER • PMCS/LEGIBRA • 03/03/2016 – 18/12/2017

- > Ensuring the front desk provides a professional and friendly service for customers
- > Ensuring the front desk provides a professional and friendly service for customers
- > Scheduling the staff bio data.
- > Liaising with other departments to ensure smooth running of all the department in the entire organizations.
- > Monitor stock and order office supplies.
- > Scheduling and arranging meetings.
- Receiving and issuing of invoices as well as receipting processes.
- > Ensure proper and costs
- > General store keeper and controller.

TECHNICAL SUPPORT EXECUTIVE AT LEGIBRA

08/04/2018-09/05/2020

- Database Design, development and administration
- > System Operations,
- System analysis
- Design and Developments
- Network System and support duties.

THE KENYA INSTITUTE OF MANAGEMENT 6TH MAY 2017 TO 3rd JUNE 2018

Diploma in Business

Management/CPA

Areas of Study

- Accounting
- Business Studies
- **Economics**
- Commerce

ST. ALBERTS CHIEPE SECONDARY SCHOOL, 2011-2014

Kenya Certificate of Secondary Education

Mean Grade B- (Minus)

ST. DOLARES ACADEMY, 2001-2010

Kenya Certificate of Primary Education.

Mean Grade B (Plain)

- > Identifying hardware and software solutions.
- > Troubleshooting technical issues.
- > Diagnosing and repairing faults.
- > Resolving network issues.
- > Installing and configuring hardware and software.
- > Speaking to customers to quickly get to the root of their problem.
- > Providing timely and accurate customer feedback.
- > Talking customers through a series of actions to resolve a problem.
- > Following up with clients to ensure the problem is resolved.
- > Replacing or repairing the necessary parts.
- > Supporting the roll-out of new applications.
- > Providing support in the form of procedural documentation.
- > Managing multiple cases at one time.
- > Testing and evaluating new technologies.
- > Conducting electrical safety checks on equipment.

CLOUD COMPUTING EXECUTIVE AT LEGIBRA AND GEOCLOUD AFRICA

01/01/2021 to date

- Experience with configuration management and automation tools
- Email configuration and troubleshooting
- Proficiency with scripting and development
- > Dns management and configurations
- Profficiency with WHM
- > CPanel management and configurations.

REFEREES

MR. ERICK KAGAI,

CTO, Legibra Solutions Limited.

+254723634326.

MS. ANNE ATIENO.

General Supervisor, PMCS.

+254762237950.

MR. WILLIAM KIAMA

Web Developer Cyber Security and Forensics Expert Geo Cloud Africa +254714849775

WALTER KIBET

Projects Manager Legibra Solutions Limited +254720274143

MS. ESTHER ATIENO,

Human Resource Manager, Legibra +254722112286

MR. MATHEW NJAGE,

Cloud Engineer, Legibra Solutions Limited +254708503222

ID NUMBER: 33214581

SEX: Male NATIONALITY: KENYAN

D.O.B: 11TH DEC 1996

EMAIL: ajwangcalvince@gmail.com

Phone Number: 0722546720